<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>sliver on text/plain</title>
    <link>https://dominicbreuker.com/categories/sliver/</link>
    <description>Recent content in sliver on text/plain</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://dominicbreuker.com/categories/sliver/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Learning Sliver C2 (10) - Sideload</title>
      <link>https://dominicbreuker.com/post/learning_sliver_c2_10_sideload/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dominicbreuker.com/post/learning_sliver_c2_10_sideload/</guid>
      <description>Sliver C2 This post is part of a tutorial blog post series on Sliver C2 (used here in version v1.5.30). For an overview: click here. As of March 6 2023, this post got a new bonus section to illustrate execution of Windows PE EXE files with sideload. The rest of the text was also updated, but only here and there.
Introduction The previous post 9 was about making a Windows implant run 3rd party tools.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning Sliver C2 (09) - Execute Assembly</title>
      <link>https://dominicbreuker.com/post/learning_sliver_c2_09_execute_assembly/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dominicbreuker.com/post/learning_sliver_c2_09_execute_assembly/</guid>
      <description>Sliver C2 This post is part of a tutorial blog post series on Sliver C2 (currently on v1.5.30). For an overview: click here.
Introduction We went through the most basic implant commands in post 8, but sometimes you may want to do a bit more than just that. Its great that your Sliver implant can read files or registry keys but it would be better if you could use it as a launchpad for all of the sophisticated attack tools that already exist out there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning Sliver C2 (08) - Implant Basics</title>
      <link>https://dominicbreuker.com/post/learning_sliver_c2_08_implant_basics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dominicbreuker.com/post/learning_sliver_c2_08_implant_basics/</guid>
      <description>Sliver C2 This post is part of a tutorial blog post series on Sliver C2. For an overview: click here. I originally wrote this based on Sliver v1.5.16, which contained a few bugs. As of March 6 2023, all content below is now updated to v1.5.34 where some bugs are removed.
Introduction If you went through the previous posts, you should be familiar with the C2 protocols and be able to write a basic stager for Sliver implants that runs even if AV is on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning Sliver C2 (07) - Stagers: Process Injection</title>
      <link>https://dominicbreuker.com/post/learning_sliver_c2_06_stagers_process_injection/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dominicbreuker.com/post/learning_sliver_c2_06_stagers_process_injection/</guid>
      <description>Sliver C2 This post is part of a tutorial blog post series on Sliver C2 (v1.5.16). For an overview: click here.
Introduction The previous post introduced basic custom stagers which run a Sliver implant within the stager process. Real malware however often injects a malicious payload into already existing processes for various reasons. The goal may be to bypass protection mechanisms or to avoid detection. For example, a browser process might be allowed to connect to the internet while other processes get blocked, or even if all processes are allowed, it may look less suspicious if it&amp;rsquo;s a browser doing that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning Sliver C2 (06) - Stagers: Basics</title>
      <link>https://dominicbreuker.com/post/learning_sliver_c2_06_stagers/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dominicbreuker.com/post/learning_sliver_c2_06_stagers/</guid>
      <description>Sliver C2 This post is part of a tutorial blog post series on Sliver C2 (v1.5.16). For an overview: click here.
Introduction Sliver C2 implants will often be delivered with a small script or program called a &amp;ldquo;stager&amp;rdquo;. Such a program downloads implant shellcode from a remote location, such as the C2 server, and then runs the shellcode. At first sight, this sounds unnecessarily complicated. Why not execute the implant directly instead of a stager?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning Sliver C2 (05) - Transports in Detail: DNS</title>
      <link>https://dominicbreuker.com/post/learning_sliver_c2_05_transports_in_detail_dns/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dominicbreuker.com/post/learning_sliver_c2_05_transports_in_detail_dns/</guid>
      <description>Sliver C2 This post is part of a tutorial blog post series on Sliver C2 (v1.5.16). For an overview: click here.
Introduction In very restricted environments, your target machine may be unable to establish connections to the Internet directly. The previous post 04 - Transports in Detail: HTTP and HTTPS was about Sliver&amp;rsquo;s HTTP-based C2 protocols, which may allow to get a C2 callback nevertheless if the target can send HTTP requests out via a proxy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning Sliver C2 (04) - Transports in Detail: HTTP and HTTPS</title>
      <link>https://dominicbreuker.com/post/learning_sliver_c2_04_transports_in_detail_http_and_https/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dominicbreuker.com/post/learning_sliver_c2_04_transports_in_detail_http_and_https/</guid>
      <description>Sliver C2 This post is part of a tutorial blog post series on Sliver C2 (v1.5.16). For an overview: click here.
Introduction This is the second post in a series about Sliver&amp;rsquo;s C2 protocols. The last one (03 - Transports in Detail: mTLS and WireGuard) was an exploration of the two most recommended and easy-to-use protocols mTLS and WireGuard. However, not all environments allow establishing such connections to your C2 infrastructure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning Sliver C2 (03) - Transports in Detail: mTLS and WireGuard</title>
      <link>https://dominicbreuker.com/post/learning_sliver_c2_03_transports_in_detail_mtls_and_wg/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dominicbreuker.com/post/learning_sliver_c2_03_transports_in_detail_mtls_and_wg/</guid>
      <description>Sliver C2 This post is part of a tutorial blog post series on Sliver C2 (v1.5.16). For an overview: click here.
Introduction After discussing Sliver beacon and session implants in general in 02 - Beacons and Sessions, I&amp;rsquo;ll now have a more detailed look at the four different C2 protocols you can choose from. This post covers the first two of them, which are mutual TLS (mTLS) and WireGuard. Both are strongly recommended in the official Getting Started Guide.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning Sliver C2 (02) - Beacons and Sessions</title>
      <link>https://dominicbreuker.com/post/learning_sliver_c2_02_beacons_and_sessions/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dominicbreuker.com/post/learning_sliver_c2_02_beacons_and_sessions/</guid>
      <description>Sliver C2 This post is part of a tutorial blog post series on Sliver C2 (v1.5.16). For an overview: click here.
Introduction This post demonstrates how to use so-called implants to remote-control a target machine from a Sliver C2 server. It is a follow-up to the previous one on Sliver C2 server installation (01 - Installation). To get familiar with the basics of Sliver, we&amp;rsquo;ll now add a (Windows) target machine to the setup.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning Sliver C2 (01) - Tutorial / Installation</title>
      <link>https://dominicbreuker.com/post/learning_sliver_c2_01_installation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dominicbreuker.com/post/learning_sliver_c2_01_installation/</guid>
      <description>Sliver C2 Introduction Recently, I developed some interest into red teaming and wanted to try out a few things. As you might know, all of that is no fun without a command and control (C2) framework. Unfortunately, most of the well-known ones are terribly expensive (Cobalt Strike or SCYTHE). Not good for a few personal experiments at home.
Fortunately though, there are plenty of open source solution out there. Check out the C2 matrix and you get more choices than you can handle.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
