<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on text/plain</title>
    <link>https://dominicbreuker.com/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on text/plain</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://dominicbreuker.com/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Hack The Box Write-up - Active</title>
      <link>https://dominicbreuker.com/post/htb_active/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dominicbreuker.com/post/htb_active/</guid>
      <description>Enumeration Port scan We start as usual with a quick masscan to get open ports as fast as possible. It returns lots of results:
$ masscan -e tun0 -p 1-65535 --rate 2000 10.10.10.100 Starting masscan 1.0.4 (http://bit.ly/14GZzcT) at 2018-09-13 20:54:40 GMT -- forced options: -sS -Pn -n --randomize-hosts -v --send-eth Initiating SYN Stealth Scan Scanning 1 hosts [65535 ports/host] Discovered open port 53/tcp on 10.10.10.100 Discovered open port 9389/tcp on 10.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hack The Box Write-up - Dropzone</title>
      <link>https://dominicbreuker.com/post/htb_dropzone/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dominicbreuker.com/post/htb_dropzone/</guid>
      <description>Enumeration Port scan As usual, start with a quick port scan to identify open ports for inspection:
 $ masscan -e tun0 -p 1-65535 --rate 2000 10.10.10.90 Starting masscan 1.0.4 (http://bit.ly/14GZzcT) at 2018-10-08 20:55:02 GMT -- forced options: -sS -Pn -n --randomize-hosts -v --send-eth Initiating SYN Stealth Scan Scanning 1 hosts [65535 ports/host]  Not a single open port was identified. Instead of debugging masscan, checking the VPN connection, trying out all sorts of firewall evasion techniques, or going crazy otherwise, remember port scans do TCP by default but can do UDP as well:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hack The Box Write-up - DevOops</title>
      <link>https://dominicbreuker.com/post/htb_devoops/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dominicbreuker.com/post/htb_devoops/</guid>
      <description>Enumeration Port scan Start with a fast standard port scan and you find only two open ports:
 $ masscan -e tun0 -p 1-65535 --rate 2000 10.10.10.91 ... Discovered open port 22/tcp on 10.10.10.91 Discovered open port 5000/tcp on 10.10.10.91  A targeted nmap scan confirms SSH on port 22 and identifies port 5000 as a Python web server, running gunicorn:
 $ nmap -sV -sC -p 22,5000 10.10.10.91 .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hack The Box Write-up - Sunday</title>
      <link>https://dominicbreuker.com/post/htb_sunday/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dominicbreuker.com/post/htb_sunday/</guid>
      <description>After quite a while, this is another write for a Hack The Box machine. This time for &amp;ldquo;Sunday&amp;rdquo;, a relatively easy machine based on Solaris. Never worked with this OS before, so I was keen to see what I would find.
Enumeration Port scan To start, we quickly scan the ports of the box. An initial scan with high rate using masscan takes only a few seconds and reveals a few open ports:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>flaws.cloud - Level 2</title>
      <link>https://dominicbreuker.com/post/flaws_cloud_2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dominicbreuker.com/post/flaws_cloud_2/</guid>
      <description>In level 1, we discovered that the homepage http://flaws.cloud is hosted in an S3 bucket with Amazons static page feature. Since the creator of the bucket configured the permissions such that unauthenticated users could list it, we discovered a secret file named &amp;ldquo;secret-dd02c7c.html&amp;rdquo;. It lead us to the start page of level 2. Now, the level description says we have to do something similar, but need our own AWS account this time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>flaws.cloud - Level 1</title>
      <link>https://dominicbreuker.com/post/flaws_cloud_lvl1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dominicbreuker.com/post/flaws_cloud_lvl1/</guid>
      <description>Adoption of cloud computing is rising rapidly. Studies predict it will soon surpass on-premises hosting also for enterprise workloads. Large corporates are hesitant mostly due to security concerns, which are partly of more general nature (&amp;ldquo;uploading data to the cloud&amp;rdquo;), but also due to the myriad of cloud security failures you read about every day in the news. For example, many companies misconfigure AWS S3 bucket permissions and leave sensitive data unprotected.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Steganography challenge - The Book of Secrets</title>
      <link>https://dominicbreuker.com/post/stego_book_of_secrets/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dominicbreuker.com/post/stego_book_of_secrets/</guid>
      <description>Steganography is the practice of hiding information inside other media like images, audio or video files, text, or pretty much anything else. It is different from encryption in that it aims not at making information unreadable but at concealing the very fact that it is there. Steganography and steganalysis (detection of steganography) are long-standing fields of research. Overviews of the field can be found, e.g., in Subhedar/Mankar (2014) or Zielińska/Mazurczyk/Szczypiorski (2014).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hack The Box Write-up - SolidState</title>
      <link>https://dominicbreuker.com/post/htb_solidstate/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dominicbreuker.com/post/htb_solidstate/</guid>
      <description>This is my second write-up for a machine from Hack The Box. It is again a rather easy one but still lots of fun. Lots of opportunities to do some oldschool telnet work on email servers. It starts with port scanning and illustrates the importance of scanning also more unpopular ports. After finding the email server with default credentials, you must use your administrator power to get code execution. Once on the box, all you have to do is finding an insecure cron job and you are root.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hack The Box Write-up - Calamity</title>
      <link>https://dominicbreuker.com/post/htb_calamity/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dominicbreuker.com/post/htb_calamity/</guid>
      <description>Hack The Box is a new company offering lab servers you can test penetration testing techniques on. It is quite educative and a lot of fun. They have multiple machines and all follow a similar pattern. You start with an IP address, have to find a way to get code execution on the machine (usually as an unprivileged user) and have to escalate from there to root. This post is about one of the machines called calamity.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>