<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on My homepage</title>
    <link>https://dominicbreuker.com/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on My homepage</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://dominicbreuker.com/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>flaws.cloud - Level 1</title>
      <link>https://dominicbreuker.com/post/flaws_cloud_lvl1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dominicbreuker.com/post/flaws_cloud_lvl1/</guid>
      <description>Adoption of cloud computing is rising rapidly. Studies predict it will soon surpass on-premises hosting also for enterprise workloads. Large corporates are hesitant mostly due to security concerns, which are partly of more general nature (&amp;ldquo;uploading data to the cloud&amp;rdquo;), but also due to the myriad of cloud security failures you read about every day in the news. For example, many companies misconfigure AWS S3 bucket permissions and leave sensitive data unprotected.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Steganography challenge - The Book of Secrets</title>
      <link>https://dominicbreuker.com/post/stego_book_of_secrets/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dominicbreuker.com/post/stego_book_of_secrets/</guid>
      <description>Steganography is the practice of hiding information inside other media like images, audio or video files, text, or pretty much anything else. It is different from encryption in that it aims not at making information unreadable but at concealing the very fact that it is there. Steganography and steganalysis (detection of steganography) are long-standing fields of research. Overviews of the field can be found, e.g., in Subhedar/Mankar (2014) or Zielińska/Mazurczyk/Szczypiorski (2014).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hack The Box Write-up - SolidState</title>
      <link>https://dominicbreuker.com/post/htb_solidstate/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dominicbreuker.com/post/htb_solidstate/</guid>
      <description>This is my second writeup for a machine from Hack The Box. It is again a rather easy one but still lots of fun. Lots of opportunities to do some oldschool telnet work on email servers. It starts with port scanning and illustrates the importance of scanning also more unpopular ports. After finding the email server with default credentials, you must use your administrator power to get code execution. Once on the box, all you have to do is finding an insecure cron job and you are root.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hack The Box Write-up - Calamity</title>
      <link>https://dominicbreuker.com/post/htb_calamity/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dominicbreuker.com/post/htb_calamity/</guid>
      <description>Hack The Box is a new company offering lab servers you can test penetration testing techniques on. It is quite educative and a lot of fun. They have multiple machines and all follow a similar pattern. You start with an IP address, have to find a way to get code execution on the machine (usually as an unprivileged user) and have to escalate from there to root. This post is about one of the machines called calamity.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>