<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>sliver on text/plain</title>
    <link>https://dominicbreuker.com/tags/sliver/</link>
    <description>Recent content in sliver on text/plain</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://dominicbreuker.com/tags/sliver/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Learning Sliver C2 (03) - Transports in Detail: mTLS and WireGuard</title>
      <link>https://dominicbreuker.com/post/learning_sliver_c2_03_transports_in_detail_mtls_and_wg/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dominicbreuker.com/post/learning_sliver_c2_03_transports_in_detail_mtls_and_wg/</guid>
      <description>Sliver C2 Introduction After discussing Sliver beacon and session implants in general in 02 - Beacons and Sessions, I&amp;rsquo;ll now have a more detailed look at the four different C2 protocols you can choose from. This post covers the first two of them, which are mutual TLS (mTLS) and WireGuard. Both are strongly recommended in the official Getting Started Guide. You can expect good performance and stable connections from both, provided that they work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning Sliver C2 (02) - Beacons and Sessions</title>
      <link>https://dominicbreuker.com/post/learning_sliver_c2_02_beacons_and_sessions/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dominicbreuker.com/post/learning_sliver_c2_02_beacons_and_sessions/</guid>
      <description>Sliver C2 Introduction This post demonstrates how to use so-called implants to remote-control a target machine from a Sliver C2 server. It is a follow-up to the previous one on Sliver C2 server installation (01 - Installation). To get familiar with the basics of Sliver, we&amp;rsquo;ll now add a (Windows) target machine to the setup. We will then see how to deliver and use a C2 agent, which Sliver calls &amp;ldquo;implant&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning Sliver C2 (01) - Installation</title>
      <link>https://dominicbreuker.com/post/learning_sliver_c2_01_installation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dominicbreuker.com/post/learning_sliver_c2_01_installation/</guid>
      <description>Sliver C2 Introduction Recently, I developed some interest into red teaming and wanted to try out a few things. As you might know, all of that is no fun without a command and control (C2) framework. Unfortunately, most of the well-known ones are terribly expensive (Cobalt Strike or SCYTHE). Not good for a few personal experiments at home.
Fortunately though, there are plenty of open source solution out there. Check out the C2 matrix and you get more choices than you can handle.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
