<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>implant on text/plain</title>
    <link>https://dominicbreuker.com/tags/implant/</link>
    <description>Recent content in implant on text/plain</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://dominicbreuker.com/tags/implant/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Learning Sliver C2 (10) - Sideload</title>
      <link>https://dominicbreuker.com/post/learning_sliver_c2_10_sideload/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dominicbreuker.com/post/learning_sliver_c2_10_sideload/</guid>
      <description>Sliver C2 This post is part of a tutorial blog post series on Sliver C2 (used here in version v1.5.30). For an overview: click here. As of March 6 2023, this post got a new bonus section to illustrate execution of Windows PE EXE files with sideload. The rest of the text was also updated, but only here and there.
Introduction The previous post 9 was about making a Windows implant run 3rd party tools.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning Sliver C2 (09) - Execute Assembly</title>
      <link>https://dominicbreuker.com/post/learning_sliver_c2_09_execute_assembly/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dominicbreuker.com/post/learning_sliver_c2_09_execute_assembly/</guid>
      <description>Sliver C2 This post is part of a tutorial blog post series on Sliver C2 (currently on v1.5.30). For an overview: click here.
Introduction We went through the most basic implant commands in post 8, but sometimes you may want to do a bit more than just that. Its great that your Sliver implant can read files or registry keys but it would be better if you could use it as a launchpad for all of the sophisticated attack tools that already exist out there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning Sliver C2 (08) - Implant Basics</title>
      <link>https://dominicbreuker.com/post/learning_sliver_c2_08_implant_basics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dominicbreuker.com/post/learning_sliver_c2_08_implant_basics/</guid>
      <description>Sliver C2 This post is part of a tutorial blog post series on Sliver C2. For an overview: click here. I originally wrote this based on Sliver v1.5.16, which contained a few bugs. As of March 6 2023, all content below is now updated to v1.5.34 where some bugs are removed.
Introduction If you went through the previous posts, you should be familiar with the C2 protocols and be able to write a basic stager for Sliver implants that runs even if AV is on.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
