<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>implant on text/plain</title>
    <link>https://dominicbreuker.com/tags/implant/</link>
    <description>Recent content in implant on text/plain</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://dominicbreuker.com/tags/implant/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Learning Sliver C2 (10) - Sideload</title>
      <link>https://dominicbreuker.com/post/learning_sliver_c2_10_sideload/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dominicbreuker.com/post/learning_sliver_c2_10_sideload/</guid>
      <description>Sliver C2 This post is part of a tutorial blog post series on Sliver C2 (used here in version v1.5.30). For an overview: click here.
Introduction The previous post 9 was about making a Windows implant run 3rd party tools. One limitation was that execute-assembly, the command we used, could only run tools written in .NET. In this post we therefore learn about the sideload command. It supports execution of native DLLs in Portable Executable (PE) format.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning Sliver C2 (09) - Execute Assembly</title>
      <link>https://dominicbreuker.com/post/learning_sliver_c2_09_execute_assembly/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dominicbreuker.com/post/learning_sliver_c2_09_execute_assembly/</guid>
      <description>Sliver C2 This post is part of a tutorial blog post series on Sliver C2 (currently on v1.5.30). For an overview: click here.
Introduction We went through the most basic implant commands in post 8, but sometimes you may want to do a bit more than just that. Its great that your Sliver implant can read files or registry keys but it would be better if you could use it as a launchpad for all of the sophisticated attack tools that already exist out there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning Sliver C2 (08) - Implant Basics</title>
      <link>https://dominicbreuker.com/post/learning_sliver_c2_08_implant_basics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dominicbreuker.com/post/learning_sliver_c2_08_implant_basics/</guid>
      <description>Sliver C2 This post is part of a tutorial blog post series on Sliver C2 (v1.5.16). For an overview: click here.
Introduction If you went through the previous posts, you should be familiar with the C2 protocols and be able to write a basic stager for Sliver implants that runs even if AV is on. Time to look at what you can do with a working C2 connection to a target, which is what this and the next posts will be about.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
