<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>AWS on text/plain</title>
    <link>https://dominicbreuker.com/categories/aws/</link>
    <description>Recent content in AWS on text/plain</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://dominicbreuker.com/categories/aws/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>flaws.cloud - Level 3</title>
      <link>https://dominicbreuker.com/post/flaws_cloud_3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dominicbreuker.com/post/flaws_cloud_3/</guid>
      <description>The previous level 2 illustrated how ACL misconfiguration can accidentally open up S3 buckets to all AWS users anywhere on the world. This was enough to just get the secret we needed. This time it will not be that easy anymore. Again, the starting point is a public website and we can use our own IAM user to list it. But now the secret is hidden.
A prerequisite for this level is to have your own AWS account with an IAM user having access to all of S3 (like in level 2).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>flaws.cloud - Level 2</title>
      <link>https://dominicbreuker.com/post/flaws_cloud_2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dominicbreuker.com/post/flaws_cloud_2/</guid>
      <description>In level 1, we discovered that the homepage http://flaws.cloud is hosted in an S3 bucket with Amazons static page feature. Since the creator of the bucket configured the permissions such that unauthenticated users could list it, we discovered a secret file named &amp;ldquo;secret-dd02c7c.html&amp;rdquo;. It lead us to the start page of level 2. Now, the level description says we have to do something similar, but need our own AWS account this time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>flaws.cloud - Level 1</title>
      <link>https://dominicbreuker.com/post/flaws_cloud_lvl1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dominicbreuker.com/post/flaws_cloud_lvl1/</guid>
      <description>Adoption of cloud computing is rising rapidly. Studies predict it will soon surpass on-premises hosting also for enterprise workloads. Large corporates are hesitant mostly due to security concerns, which are partly of more general nature (&amp;ldquo;uploading data to the cloud&amp;rdquo;), but also due to the myriad of cloud security failures you read about every day in the news. For example, many companies misconfigure AWS S3 bucket permissions and leave sensitive data unprotected.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>